- 얘들아
- 왔어?
It is true what they say:
역시 임산부 배는
드럼처럼 보이네
Pregnant bellies look like a drum.
I'm so pregnant that
my guitar doesn't fit anymore.
배가 너무 나와서
기타를 맬 수가 없어
애 낳을 때까진 드럼으로
반주할 거야, 진짜 근사해
So I'm going to play my songs
on this drum.
It sounds really cool!
한번 들어봐
Listen, listen.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
냄새나는 고양이
대체 뭘 먹었니
What are they feeding you?
대단한데
That sounds great!
내가 뭐랬어
겨우 한 시간 연습한 거야
I know! And I've only
been playing for an hour.
- 피비, 저예요
- 어서 와요
-What are you doing here?
-I came to ask you a big favor.
웬일이에요?
중요한 부탁이 있어서 왔어요
Don't tell me you want to keep
more stuff in my uterus.
내 뱃속에 또 뭔가를
넣어달라는 건 아니죠?
아니에요
Okay. Now, see.
뭐냐면...
I want to name the girl baby Leslie.
딸아이는 레슬리란
이름을 붙일 거고
And Frank wants to name
one of the boy babies...
프랭크는 두 아들 중 하나를
프랭크 2세 2세라고 부른대요
...Frank Jr., Jr.
Wouldn't that be Frank lll?
프랭크 3세가 아니구요?
또 시작하기 싫어요
Don't get me started.
Anyway, since there
are three babies...
어쨌든 아기가 셋이잖아요
두 아이에겐 우리 이름을
붙였으니까
...and we both got
to put our names in...
...we would be truly honored
if you would name the other boy baby.
나머지 사내애 한 명은 피비가
이름을 지어줬으면 고맙겠어요
와! 그거 영광이네요
That's so nice!
오오! 쿠거...
Cougar.
Think about it.
잘 생각해봐요
The One with Rachel's New Dress
욕실에 브라를 널어놨어
벤이 아빠 건 줄 알고 놀랄 텐데
I left a bra drying in there.
Will your son think it's yours
and be traumatized?
엄마한테 마누라가 있는데
아빠가 브라를 못하겠어?
Mommy can have a wife.
Daddy can have a bra.
It's time to go.
가야겠어
아냐, 저 시계 빨라
See, that clock's a little fast.
아직 17분이나 남았잖아
We still have 17 minutes.
17분 동안 뭘 할 수 있을까
두 번 정도
What can we do in 17 minutes...
...twice?
Well, that's ambitious.
욕심도 많으셔
You can ignore that.
못 들은 걸로 해
캐롤하고 벤이야
That's your son.
크면 다 이해할 거야
Believe me, when he's older,
he'll understand.
로스?
금방 나갈게, 흐미...
I'll be right there.
안녕
- 어서 와
- 그래
- 오셨네
- 안녕하세요
This is Carol and Susan.
에밀리, 캐롤하고 수잔이야
-It's so nice to finally meet you.
-You too.
- 얘기 많이 들었어요
- 저두요
-Susan will be in London next week.
-I've never been there.
수잔이 다음주에 런던에서
광고를 찍는대요
런던은 처음이라
무척 기대돼요
- 내가 안내할게요
- 그래주면 고맙죠
-I'll show you around.
-Great!
Also, I was hoping to catch a show.
Any suggestions?
연극도 보고 싶은데
추천 좀 해주세요
There's tons of terrific stuff.
좋은 작품은 많죠
I'll go with you.
같이 가요
친해지는 것도 좋지만
비행기 시간에 늦겠어
Look at you two bonding.
Making us late for the airport.
Are you all right?
- 자기 괜찮아?
- 걱정 말아요
It's just us getting along
is difficult for him...
봐주기 힘들 거예요
날 싫어하니까
...because he doesn't like me.
무슨 말이에요, 그건...
사실이야
Come on. That's....
It's true.
How did we lose?
어떻게 둘 다 지냐?
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
Do we have a baby name yet?
아기 이름 지었어?
No. It's so hard!
아니, 너무 어려워
작명책에도 마땅한 게 없고
I went through this book
and found nothing.
I want a name that's
really strong and confident.
난 강하고 자신만만한 이름이
좋은데, 가령 엑손정유처럼
You know? Like...Exxon!
It certainly worked
for that Valdez kid.
발데즈 지방에선 잘 통하겠다
강한 이름이 좋다면
헐크는 어때
You want a strong name?
How about The Hulk?
I'm not sure about Hulk,
but I like a name starting with "The".
뜻은 그럴 듯한데
어감은 영 아니다
조이도 쓸 만한 이름이지
You want a good name,
go with Joey.
Joey's your pal, your buddy.
조이는 네 친구
조이는 너의 벗
'다들 어디 갔어?'
'조이랑 놀지요'
Where is everybody?
They're hanging out with Joey!
조이 이름을 따려면
차라리 챈들러가 나아
If you're going to name him Joey,
you should name him Chandler.
Chandler's funny, sophisticated,
and very lovable...
챈들러는 재미있고 품위 있고
사랑스러워, 일단 알고 보면
...once you get to know him.
조이도 사랑스러워
Joey's lovable too.
But with Joey, if you need him,
he'll be there.
게다가 조이는 필요할 때
항상 곁에 있어주지
챈들러도 곁에 있을 거야
한발 늦을 수도 있지만
Chandler will be there too.
He might be a little late...
...but he'll be there.
And he'll bring you cold soda...
네가 덥고 갈증 날 때 부르면
시원한 음료수를 대령할게
...if what you need him for
is that you're really hot.
What do you say?
자, 어떡할래
I like the idea of naming him
after someone I love.
사랑하는 친구의 이름도
나쁠 건 없지
Joey and Chandler
are both great names.
조이와 챈들러
둘 다 근사해
하지만...
좋아, 난 그냥...
헐크라고 지을까 봐
All right, I don't
Maybe I'll just name him The Hulk.
I shouldn't have mentioned it.
I wanted to name my kid that.
괜히 알려줬네
내 아들 이름인데
모니카, 네가 처음으로 조슈아와
밤을 보낸다면 어떤 속옷 입을래
If you hoped to sleep with Joshua,
which one would you wear?
It creeps me out choosing
other people's sex clothes.
그거 아니? 남의 잠자리 의상
골라주는 거 닭살 돋는다
I'm sorry. I'm just so excited.
미안
가슴이 다 벌렁거려
얼마나 기다렸던 순간인데
I've been waiting for months.
I got my hair colored.
머리도 염색했지
침대시트도 갈았지
I got new sheets.
I'm making him a very fancy meal.
근사한 요리도 준비할 거야
What am I making him, by the way?
내가 만드는 요리가 뭐지?
A frisee salad
with goat cheese and pine nuts...
고트치즈와 잣이 들어간
프리즈 샐러드와
...wild rice, roasted asparagus
and salmon en croute.
와일드 라이스
아스파라거스볶음에 연어찜
I thought I was making him
filet mignon.
난 내가 등심구이
만드는 줄 알았는데
You decided to make salmon
because you had some left over.
식당에 남는 연어가 있어서
넌 마음을 바꾼 거야
Then you realized if you bitched,
then you would stop cooking...
너! 계속 징징거리면
넌! 요리 집어치울 거고
...and you would have to make your
famous baked potato and Diet Coke.
너한테는 구운 감자와
다이어트콜라만 남게 돼
I really get crabby when I cook.
나 요리할 때 되게 무섭다
Why go through all this trouble?
He's a guy.
이럴 것까진 없는데
그 사람도 남자야
You'd serve the potato and he'd
still want to have sex with you.
감자만 대접해도
너랑 자려고 할 거야
그건 내 방식이 아니올시다
That is not how I operate.
We've got to get a new game.
이제 다른 게임으로 바꾸자
- 나 왔어
- 어서 와
So Emily called last night.
에밀리가 어젯밤에 전화했어
And now you're giving me the message?
그걸 이제야 전해 주냐?
Turns out that Emily is
just crazy about Susan.
수잔이 너무나 맘에 든대
그래, 함께 극장에도 가고
They're going
to the theater together.
They're going to dinner.
함께 저녁도 먹고
They're going horseback riding!
함께 말도 탈 거래
God, Susan is so fun!
수잔 진짜 놀 줄 안다
Look, this is just
a little too familiar.
약간 낯익은 상황 같지 않아?
For six months
before Carol and I split up...
캐롤은 이혼 6개월 전부터
입이 닳도록 얘기했어
...all I heard was,
"My friend Susan is so smart.
'내 친구 수잔은 진짜 똑똑해'
My friend Susan is so funny.
My friend Susan is so great."
'내 친구 수잔은 진짜 재미있어'
'내 친구 수잔은 진짜 짱이야'
You think something could happen
between Emily and Susan?
설마 에밀리와 수잔 사이를
의심하는 건 아니겠지?
Hey, they're going
to the gym together!
같이 헬스클럽에도 다닌대
Two women...
여자 둘이서...
다리 좍좍 벌리고
...stretching!
한증막에서 장난도 치면서...
'퍼스널 베스트'도 못 봤어?
They take a steam, things get playful.
Didn't you see Personal Best?
No, but I'm gonna!
아니, 꼭 봐야겠다
Hi! You're crazy.
이것 보슈, 댁은 미쳤어
에밀리는 레즈비언이 아냐
Emily is straight.
How do you know?
We thought Carol was straight.
어떻게 알아, 결혼 전엔
캐롤도 정상인 줄 알았어
그래, 로스란 이름은 싫다
Yeah, definitely.
I don't like the name Ross.
What a weird way to kick me
when I'm down!
자빠진 사람
콱콱 밟아라
No, I meant for the baby.
아냐, 아기 이름 때문에 그래
What's wrong with Ross?
로스가 어디가 어때서
Something like this would never
happen to The Hulk, you know.
헐크라면 이런 일은
안 당했을 거 아냐
That's not true.
모르는 소리 마
In The Incredible Hulk, number 72,
Dr. Bruce Banner found....
'두 얼굴의 사나이' 72회에서
브루스 배너 박사는...
You know....
몰라, 관두자
내 애인은 레즈비언이야
Never mind.
My girlfriend's a lesbian.
I'm definitely going to go
with either Joey or Chandler.
조이나 챈들러 중
하나를 고를 거야
그럼 조이지
You gotta pick Joey!
Name one famous person
named Chandler.
유명인사 중에
챈들러란 사람 있어?
Raymond Chandler.
레이몬드 챈들러
Someone you didn't make up.
지어낸 인물 말고
There are no famous Joeys.
Except for...
유명한 조이는 있냐?
조이 버타푸코만 빼고
...Joey Buttafucco.
Yeah, that guy really hurt us.
그 작자는 가문의 수치야
그럼 타협을 하자
이건 어때... 챈노이
How about a compromise then?
What if it's...
...Chan-no-ey?
Joey? Think about it.
He'll never be President.
조이라고? 잘 생각해봐
조이란 대통령이 나올 거 같아?
There will never be a President Joey.
I didn't want to bring this up.
나도 이런 말까진 하기 싫지만
Chandler is the stupidest name
I've heard in my life!
챈들러? 내 평생 그렇게
거지같은 이름은 못 들어봤다
헉!
It's not a name!
It's barely even a word.
그게 이름이냐?
단어라고도 할 수 없어, 알아?
샹들리에랑 비슷하지만 아냐!
It's like chandelier
but it's not!
게다가 '빙'까지 붙여봐
자던 소가 웃는다
Then, you put it together with Bing
and forget about it.
It's a stupid, stupid, non-name!
거지발싸개 같은 이름이야
그래...
You're right.
I have a horrible, horrible name.
맞아, 내 이름은
정말 끔찍해
I'm sorry, man. I'm sorry.
- 미안하다, 내가 심했어
- 괜찮아
그럼 조이다!
So I guess it's Joey then.
This is so nice.
Thank you for doing this.
너무 멋지군요
애 많이 썼어요
무슨 말씀, 요리는
마음의 평화랍니다
Please! Cooking soothes me.
이제 먹을까요?
So dig in!
그러죠, 너무 먹음직스러워요
It all looks so good.
Oh, my God.
맙소사
I know.
My God, this rice is so
알아요, 내 솜씨지만
정말 환상적이네요
I am so good!
저 뒤에
Behind you.
미안해요, 전에 여기 살아서
가끔 철새도래지로 착각하죠
They used to live here,
and sometimes they migrate back over.
Is there some way
that they could not be here?
쟤들 좀 내보내면 안 될까요?
날개 달린 짐승은 딱 질색이라
Farm birds really
kind of freak me out!
- 네, 그러죠 뭐
- 좋아요
어서 가거라
Here we go.
There you go!
나가자
Hey! How'd you do that?
재주 참 용타!
들어가자
All gone.
이제 없어요
날개 달린 짐승?
So, farm birds, huh?
유일하게 별난 점이죠
정말이에요
It's my only weird thing, I swear.
I would have told you.
I didn't know that they'd be here.
미리 말할 수도 있었지만
여기 그런 게 있을 줄이야
이제 됐어요
좋아요
내가 이걸 좀...
왜 또 그래요?
Can I serve you a little
What?
Nothing.
아니에요, 밖에 있다고
생각하니까 불편해서
It's just that I know
that they're still out there.
복도 건너편이에요
문이 두 개나 있고
They're across the hall.
That's two doors away.
그걸 다 쪼아내려면
한세월 걸릴 걸요
It'll take them a long time
to peck their way back over here.
별로 안 웃긴데
That's not funny.
좋아요, 그럼...
Would you feel better
if we went someplace else?
장소를 옮기면 괜찮을까요?
다 싸들고 당신 집으로 가요
We could pack this stuff up
and go to your apartment.
수리 중이라 엉망이에요
They're working on it.
It's a mess.
I'm staying at my parents' house.
We could go there.
지금 부모님 댁에 있는데
거기로 갈까요?
- 부모님 댁?
- 네, 여행가셨어요
They're out of town.
넓고 전망도 좋아서
꽤 로맨틱할 거예요
It's a huge place,
and it's got this gorgeous view.
It'd be very romantic.
-What do you say?
-Yeah, that works.
어때요
네, 괜찮아요
짓궂은 놈들이네
They can smell the fear.
- 어서 와
- 안녕
벤은?
How's Ben?
뭐 먹겠냐고 물어봤더니 싫대
I asked if he wanted to eat.
He said no.
I asked if he wanted to sleep.
잘 거냐고 했더니 그것도 싫대
그럼 뭘 하고 싶냐고 물었더니
그것도 싫다면서
I asked what he wanted to do.
He said no.
So he's sweeping.
지금 청소하고 있어
엄마 왔다
안녕?
수잔한테서 연락 왔어?
Any word from Susan?
에밀리하고 너무너무
재미있게 보내고 있대
She said she's having
so much fun with Emily.
By the by, did it
ever occur to you that...
혹시 그런 생각 안 들어?
두 사람이 좀 과하게
즐기고 있다든가...
...maybe they might be having
a little too much fun?
What's too much fun?
과하게 즐기다니
우리가 같이 살 때
당신과 수잔이 그랬듯이
The kind of fun you and Susan had
when we were married.
Oh, my God!
You are so paranoid.
- 저런, 편집증이 심하네
- 내가?
Am l?
- 그래
- 이 몸이?
Am l?
에밀리는 잘 모르겠지만
수잔과 난 사랑하는 사이야
Susan is in a loving,
committed relationship.
Carol, so were we.
캐롤, 우리도 그랬어
잠깐 상상을 해봐
Just imagine for a moment...
수잔이 누군가를 만났는데
서로 강한 호감을 느꼈어
...that Susan meets someone,
and they hit it off.
가령 함께 극장에 다녀오다
술집에 들러 한 잔 한다
They're coming back from the theater,
and they stop at a pub for drinks.
즐겁게 웃고 떠들다
한쪽이 무심코 상대를 만진다
They're laughing.
Someone innocently
touches someone else.
짜릿한 불꽃이 튀는데
새롭고 강렬한 느낌이다
There's electricity.
It's new. It's exciting.
Are you saying there isn't
the slightest possibility...
그런 사태가 발생할 확률이
눈곱만큼도 없다는 거야?
...of something happening?
가능성은 있지
-Maybe.
-Oh, my God!
돌겠네! 그 말 듣기 전엔
나도 믿고 싶지 않았어!
I didn't really believe it
until you just said it!
다른 애들은 안 믿었지만
그 오리가 진짜 날 밀었어요
None of the other kids believed me,
but I swear that duck pushed me.
와! 집이 너무 근사해요
This place is fabulous!
This is the downstairs living room.
네, 지금 이건
아래층 거실이고...
그럼 거실이 두 개예요?
There's two living rooms?
Growing up here, this place
must have been a real babe magnet.
이런 집에서 자랐으면
여자애들 엄청 꼬였겠다
It would have been,
but my parents just moved here.
애석하지만 이사 오신 지
얼마 안 됐어요
어쨌든 여자애들
대따 꼬이는 집이에요
You should know this place
is a real babe magnet.
증명해줘요?
Want to make out?
Why don't I put the food
in the fridge...
이렇게 합시다
음식은 냉장고에 뒀다
나중에 먹는 게 어때요
...and we can eat it later?
That sounds like a plan.
멋진 계획이네요
Is there a place
that I could go freshen up?
여기 씻는 데가 어디죠?
그래요
Just down the hall
and second door to your left.
복도를 따라가다
왼쪽으로 두 번째 문
집에 있었구나
-Hi, darling.
-What are you doing here?
어떻게 된 거죠?
-We cut the trip short.
-France sucks!
- 중간에 그냥 돌아왔다
- 프랑스는 밥맛이더라
This may be a little weird,
but I've got a date here.
이걸 어쩌죠?
여자친구가 와있는데
그만하면 알겠다
Say no more.
We'll grab some food, go upstairs
and be out of your hair.
우린 먹을 것 챙겨서 위층으로
올라갈 테니까 신경 쓰지 마라
That'd be great.
So you didn't get to ltaly?
그래주시면 좋죠
이태리에도 안 가셨어요?
그래, 밥맛이야
Yep. Sucks!
Hi, you!
어서 와요
하느님 맙소사...
Oh, my God!
그래요, 난 요리만
잘하는 게 아니랍니다
I know. I can do more than cook.
I like her. She seems smart.
마음에 든다
똑똑해 보여
레이첼, 부모님이세요
Rachel, my parents.
오, 뵙게 돼서 기쁘네요
So nice to meet you.
안녕하세요
반갑습니다, 부인
조슈아, 그 500달러를
생필품 마련에 쓴 게로구나
Joshua, that $500 was for groceries.
What, this? Oh, no.
That's not what it is.
네? 이거요? 아뇨
그런 게 아니에요
전 패션 쪽 일을 해요
Okay, I work in fashion.
이건 사실 드레스랍니다
And this is a real dress, actually.
밀라노에서 많이 입죠
They're wearing it in Milan.
Part of my job is to wear the clothes
and see how people respond.
제 업무의 일부예요
이렇게 옷을 입어보고 대중의
반응을 상사들한테 보고하죠
Then I report back to my superiors
at Bloomingdale's.
Obviously, in this case...
이 옷의 경우엔 보고서에
여러 말 쓸 거 없겠네요
...I am going to report back:
"U.S.A. not ready."
미국에선 시기상조다
Maybe in L.A.
- LA는 괜찮을 거예요
- 맞아요
There you go!
그렇죠
Have you kids eaten yet?
두 사람은 저녁 먹었나?
일 치른 후에 먹으려고, 아니!
We were going to do that after.
I mean, next.
먹죠 뭐
Why don't we all
get something to eat?
우린 시장한데
함께 외식이나 할까?
네, 좋아요
No use wasting this baby
just lying around the house.
집안에서 뒹굴면서
이 멋진 옷을 썩힐 순 없죠
그럼 나갑시다
So we'll go eat.
You'll wear that.
아가씨는 그걸 입고
We'll be eating and,
of course, you'll be wearing that.
저녁을 먹는 거요
물론 그걸 걸치고
아까 일은 내가 사과할게
I am sorry about what I said.
Nope, you're right.
It is a ridiculous name!
아냐, 네 말이 맞아
정말 웃기는 이름이야
It's not bad.
- 그 정도는 아냐
- 그렇다니까!
Yes, it is!
From now on, I have no first name.
지금부터 난 이름 없어
그럼 '빙'만 남는데
You're just Bing?
I have no name.
성까지 없애자
So what are we supposed to call you?
그럼 널 뭐라고 부르지?
좋아, 당분간은
이렇게 불러줘
Okay, for now, temporarily,
you can call me...
...Clint.
클린트...
No way are you cool enough
to pull off "Clint."
클린트까지 넘볼 정도로
멋진 인물은 아닐 텐데...
What name am l
cool enough to pull off?
그럼 어느 선까지
넘볼 수 있지?
진...
Gene.
It's Clint.
클린트야, 클린트라고
It's Clint!
Bye, Gene.
- 이따 보자, 진
- 잘 가, 진
It's Clint!
클린트야, 클린트!
진이 왜 저러지?
What's up with Gene?
- 잠옷 입고 외식을 했어?
- 그래
You wore your nightie to dinner?
The best part was when the waiter
spilled water down my back.
최고의 장면은 웨이터가
내 등에 물을 쏟는 통에
I jumped up and my boob popped out.
내가 펄쩍 뛰다
가슴이 튀어나온 거였어
내가 못살아
It's all right.
I got nice boobs.
괜찮아, 내 가슴 예쁘니까
I just picked up
a message from Emily.
에밀리가 메시지를 남겼는데
수잔하고 시낭송회에 갈 거래
She and Susan are going
to a poetry reading together.
-So?
그래서?
그래서? 시라니까
Poetry?
Susan's gay.
수잔은 동성애자야
They're being gay together!
동성애 놀이를 하잖아
Emily's straight.
에밀리는 아냐
꿈도 야무지셔!
Oh, wake up!
Carol really messed you up.
캐롤이 사람 하나
완전히 망쳐놨네
Excuse me?
뭐라고?
그 여자 때문에 넌 의심과
질투에 눈먼 알랑쇠가 됐어
She turned you into
this untrusting, crazy, jealous...
...sycophant!
So I don't know what "sycophant" means,
but the rest is right.
그래, 알랑쇠의 뜻은 모르지만
나머지는 다 사실이야
What are you talking about?
I am not a crazy, jealous person.
난 절대 질투에
눈먼 사람이 아냐
허!
뭐가
She's right.
바른 말했네
When we were together, you got upset
about Mark, and there was nothing.
나랑 사귈 때 아무 죄도 없는
마크 때문에 생난리를 쳤잖아
This makes sense.
- 듣고 보니 그러네?
- 그렇긴 뭐가 그래!
It does not!
맞아
In high school,
you weren't jealous at all...
고등학교 땐 사귀던 애들이 몽땅
뒤에서 딴 짓 해도 질투 안 했잖아
...even though all your girlfriends
cheated on you.
그니까 92년, 93년까지는
사람을 의심하지 않았는데
So up until '92, '93,
he was very trusting.
Then '94 hit, Carol left him,
and bam! Paranoid City!
94년에 캐롤이 떠나자 쿵!
과대망상이 나타난 거야
그래
Absolutely!
- 정확히 짚었어
- 진짜 재미있다
This is so fun!
This is not fun!
재미 한 개도 없다!
All we're trying to say is...
오빠
캐롤 때문에 에밀리와의
관계마저 그르치면 안돼
...don't let what happened with Carol
ruin what you've got with Emily.
The '92 Ross wouldn't.
92년표 로스는 안 그래
알았어
I still think I was right
about that Mark thing.
그래도 마크 건은 내가 옳았어
뭐? 하나 알려줄까?
에밀리도 레즈비언이면 좋겠다
Well, you know what?
I hope Emily is a lesbian.
Drumroll.
드럼롤이야
좋아, 이제 됐어
All right.
Help!
도와줘
Am I a Mark or a John?
마크로 할까
존으로 할까
You're not tall enough to be a Mark.
마크로선 키가 좀 작아
But you might make a good Barney.
하지만 바니는 잘 어울린다
Look, I am serious.
농담 아냐, 내일 3시 반에
법원에 갈 거라고
Tomorrow at 3:30, I'm going
to the courthouse.
You're going through with this?
진짜로 바꿀 거야?
이름 하나 때문에
왕창 꼬인 인생이야
This name has held me back
my entire life.
It's why kids picked on me
and why I never do well with women.
학교에선 왕따 되고
여자들한텐 찬밥 되고
So tomorrow, I'll either be
Mark Johnson or John Markson.
내일 4시면 마크 존슨이나
존 마크슨이 돼있을 거야
You've got problems because of you,
not your name!
문제는 이름이 아니라 너야
거기까지만 해둬
This has got to stop!
Chandler is a great name.
챈들러가 얼마나 좋은
이름인데, 사실 난...
In fact....
그래
I'm sorry, I know you wanted me
to name the baby Joey.
네 마음은 충분히 이해해
하지만, 끄응... 난...
I'm going to name the baby Chandler.
챈들러로 결정했어
Really?
진짜야?
But you have to keep the name too.
대신 너도 이름 바꾸지 마
Okay, thanks!
- 알았어, 고마워
- 그래
You want to hug it out?
- 포옹으로 마무리?
- 좋지
참! 동생부부한테
당장 알려야겠다
I'm going to go tell
Frank and Alice right now!
그래
Bye, Pheebs!
- 잘 가, 피비
- 그래, 안녕
004편이 17번 게이트로
도착합니다
-Nice luggage.
-I was going to say.
- 가방 멋진데
- 그러게
나야
- 보고 싶었어
- 나도
I missed you too.
에밀리, 덕분에
정말 즐거웠어요
-Thanks, I had a great time.
-So did l.
나두요
혀는 안 쓰네
No tongue.